Wyck Association Collection 1663-1972 Mss.Ms.Coll.52
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Correspondence, 1676-1971; 31.0 Linear feet 80 boxes
  - To: Robert Bowne Haines II
    - Scripture Gift Mission, 1928 Feb.8-1928 Mar.27 (Box 63, Folder 1131)
    - Scripture Gift Mission, 1928 Apr.3-1928 Apr.27 (Box 63, Folder 1132)
    - Scripture Gift Mission, 1928 May 4-1928 May 29 (Box 63, Folder 1133)
    - Scripture Gift Mission, 1928 Jun.6-1928 Jul.21 (Box 63, Folder 1134)
    - Scripture Gift Mission, 1928 Aug.1-1928 Aug.21 (Box 63, Folder 1135)
    - Scripture Gift Mission Letters from Africa, 1928 Sep.4-1928 Oct.19 (Box 63, Folder 1136)
    - Letters from Africa Scripture Gift Mission, 1928 Nov.10-1928 Dec.24 (Box 63, Folder 1137)
    - 1929 Feb.29-1929 Aug.22 (Box 63, Folder 1138)
    - 1929 Sep.5-1929 Dec.28 (Box 63, Folder 1139)
    - 1930 Jan.8-1039 Mar.31 (Box 63, Folder 1140)
    - 1930 Apr.25-1930 May 28 (Box 63, Folder 1141)
    - Haines Gauge Co., 1930 Jun.30-1930 Nov.21 (Box 63, Folder 1142)
    - Haines Gauge Co. Mennonite Church, 1931 Feb.14-1931 Jun.30 (Box 63, Folder 1143)
    - 1931 Jul.3-1931 Dec.9 (Box 63, Folder 1144)
    - Mexican Missions in California Scripture Gift Mission, 1932 Jan.29-1935 Oct.22 (Box 63, Folder 1145)
  - From: Mary Morton Haines
    - Lake Mohawk, N. Y.; original poetry; Abington Meeting, 1866 Dec.24-1873 Oct.12 (Box 64, Folder 1146)
    - Jay Cooke; Funeral of Luke Morris; Isaac J. Wistar, 1874 Jan.29-1885 Oct.23 (Box 64, Folder 1147)
    - Horticulture; California Trip (descriptions); Japanese Trip, 1888 May 18-1890 (Box 64, Folder 1148)
    - Addition of new wing to "Heidelberg", Cheltenhm, Pa. Horticulature; Rockwood pottery, 1891 Aug.3-1892 (Box 64, Folder 1149)
    - Letters from Japan, 1893 Mar.8-1894 Jul.6 (Box 64, Folder 1150)
    - Charles J. Wister, Death of Thomas Stewardson, "Dr. Rhoad's meetings", 1897 Oct.7-1902 Oct.13 (Box 64, Folder 1151)
    - Trip to Japan Horticulture, 1903 Jan.8-1903 Oct.31 (Box 64, Folder 1152)
    - Horticulture, Mrs. Owen J. Wister; Mantle Fielding, 1904 Jan.8-1904 May 19 (Box 64, Folder 1153)
    - 1906 Mar.12-1908 Apr.11 (Box 64, Folder 1154)
    - 1909 Feb.12-1912 Nov.22 (Box 64, Folder 1155)
    - Settlement of Estate of Margaret Vaux Wistar Haines, 1917 Nov.15-1917 Nov.22 (Box 64, Folder 1156)
    - 1919 Jul.23-1927 Jan.31 (Box 64, Folder 1157)
    - Fragments, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1158)
  - To: Mary Morton Haines (cont.)
    - William Forster Home, 1866 Dec.4-1889 Oct.2 (Box 64, Folder 1159)
    - Germantown Hospital; Needlework Guild; Japanese correspondence; Friends' Mission, 1890 Jul.15-1897 Aug.14 (Box 64, Folder 1160)
    - Japanese Correspondence, 1898 Apr.28-1903 Sep.16 (Box 64, Folder 1161)
    - 1907 Nov.12-1912 Dec.26 (Box 64, Folder 1162)
    - 1914 May 5-1916 Mar.27 (Box 64, Folder 1163)
    - Estate of Margaret V. W. Haines, 1917 Aug.8-1917 Dec.21 (Box 64, Folder 1164)
    - Estate of Margaret V. H. Haines, 1918 Feb.18-1918 Jul.15 (Box 64, Folder 1165)
    - Estate of Margaret V. W. Haines, 1918 Aug.2-1918 Dec.16 (Box 64, Folder 1166)
    - Estate of Margaret V. W. Haines Estate of Isaac J. Wistar, 1919 Jan.8-1920 Aug.6 (Box 64, Folder 1167)
    - 1921 Jan.10-1925 Jul.8 (Box 64, Folder 1168)
    - 1927 Jan.13-1942 Jul.15 (Box 64, Folder 1169)
    - n.d. (Box 64, Folder 1170)
  - From: William J. Haines
    - 1872 Jun.24-1908 Apr.7 (Box 65, Folder 1171)
    - 1909 Apr.13-1923 Apr.21 (Box 65, Folder 1172)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1916 Jun.5-1916 Nov.23 (Box 65, Folder 1173)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1917 Mar.22-1917 Dec.26 (Box 65, Folder 1174)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1918 Jan.3-1918 Dec.16 (Box 65, Folder 1175)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1919 Mar.11-1920 Mar.18 (Box 65, Folder 1176)
  - To: William J. Haines
    - Franklin Institute, 1872 - 1885 (Box 65, Folder 1177)
    - Franklin Institute Electricity, 1886 Sep.6 1886 Oct.25 (Box 65, Folder 1178)
    - 1886 Mar.18-1899 May 5 (Box 65, Folder 1179)
    - Founder's Day, Germantown, 1908, 1906 Oct.24-1909 Oct.27 (Box 65, Folder 1180)
    - 1910 Apr.20-1925 Feb.20 (Box 65, Folder 1181)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1915 Oct.14-1916 Dec.7 (Box 65, Folder 1182)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1917 Jan.19-1917 Jul.28 (Box 65, Folder 1183)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1917 Aug.1-1917 Aug.31 (Box 65, Folder 1184)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1917 Sep.4-1917 Oct.31 (Box 65, Folder 1185)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1917 Nov.1-1917 Nov.27 (Box 65, Folder 1186)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1917 Dec.7-1917 Dec.26 (Box 65, Folder 1187)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1918 Jan.3-1918 Dec.18 (Box 65, Folder 1188)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1919 Sep.11-1919 Aug.26 (Box 65, Folder 1189)
    - Hawkins Lumber Co., 1920 Feb.14-1921 Jan.9 (Box 65, Folder 1190)
  - From: Jane Bowne Haines II
    - 1874 Mar.-1879 Dec. (Box 66, Folder 1191)
    - 1880 Jan.22-1881 June (Box 66, Folder 1192)
    - 1881 July - 1883 Aug.23 (Box 66, Folder 1193)
    - 1884 Jan.3-1890 Aug.6 (Box 66, Folder 1194)
    - 1891 Jul.17-1895 Apr.29 (Box 66, Folder 1195)
    - 1897 Aug.18-1898 Sep.14 (Box 66, Folder 1196)
    - 1899 Apr.4-1899 Dec.12 (Box 66, Folder 1197)
    - 1900 Feb.1-1900 Oct.10 (Box 66, Folder 1198)
    - Letters from Mexico, 1901 Jan.22-1902 Nov.6 (Box 66, Folder 1199)
    - 1903 Jan.14-1903 Mar.29 (Box 66, Folder 1200)
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1903 Apr.4-1903 May 22 (Box 66, Folder 1201)
    - Assessment - family owned land, 1903 Jun.6-1903 Nov.24 (Box 66, Folder 1202)
    - 1904 Jan.20 1904 Dec.19 (Box 66, Folder 1203)
    - Building greenhouse, 1905 Jan.10-1905 Dec.14 (Box 66, Folder 1204)
    - Letters from Europe Letters from Mexico, 1906 Jan.4-1910 Dec.11 (Box 66, Folder 1205)
    - Caspar Wistar manuscripts sent to the Historical Society of Pennsylvania, Wistar Rose celebration, 1914 Sep.26-1928 Aug.4 (Box 66, Folder 1206)
    - Genealogy - Hans Milan, 1930 Mar.24-1933 (Box 66, Folder 1207)
    - Genealogy - Bowne, Hartshorne, Marshall, Saltar; Raspberry vinegar; Armitt-Waln marriage certificate, 1934 Apr.10-1935 Nov. (Box 66, Folder 1208)
    - Genealogy, 1936 Jan.20-1936 Mar.4 (Box 66, Folder 1209)
    - Genealogy - Hans Milan, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 1210)
  - To: Jane Bowne Haines II
    - 1875 Mar.24-1877 Feb.4 (Box 67, Folder 1211)
    - 1883 May 11-1891 Sep.29 (Box 67, Folder 1212)
    - 1892 Mar.30-1895 Sep.9 (Box 67, Folder 1213)
    - 1896 Jan.1-1896 Aug.19 (Box 67, Folder 1214)
    - 1901 May 26-1902 Sep.22 (Box 67, Folder 1215)
    - 1903 Jan.17 - 1905 Aug.4 (Box 67, Folder 1216)
    - 1906 Feb.24-1909 Oct.18 (Box 67, Folder 1217)
    - 1910 Feb.23-1910 Nov.10 (Box 67, Folder 1218)
    - 1911 Mar.31-1911 Jun.29 (Box 67, Folder 1219)
    - 1912 May 21-1912 Dec.12 (Box 67, Folder 1220)
    - 1913 Mar.13-1916 Nov.14 (Box 67, Folder 1221)
    - Electrical work at Wyck, 1917 Feb.15-1918 Oct.11 (Box 67, Folder 1222)
    - 1919 Feb.24-1920 Dec.16 (Box 67, Folder 1223)
    - 1921 Apr.21-1923 Nov.21 (Box 67, Folder 1224)
    - 1924 May 21-1925 Apr.8 (Box 67, Folder 1225)
    - 1926 Mar.5-1928 Dec.12 (Box 67, Folder 1226)
    - 1929 Jan.4-1929 Mar.27 (Box 67, Folder 1227)
    - 1929 Apr.5-1929 May 24 (Box 67, Folder 1228)
    - 1929 Jun.3-1929 Nov.18 (Box 67, Folder 1229)
    - 1930 Jan.13-1930 Oct.10 (Box 67, Folder 1230)
    - 1931 Mar.21-1931 Jun.13 (Box 67, Folder 1231)
    - 1932 Jan.20-1932 Dec.22 (Box 67, Folder 1232)
    - 1933 Jan.11-1933 Jun.15 (Box 67, Folder 1233)
    - 1933 Jul.10-1933 Dec.21 (Box 67, Folder 1234)
    - 1934 Jan.3-1934 Jun.30 (Box 68, Folder 1235)
    - 1934 Jul.10-1934 Aug.27 (Box 68, Folder 1236)
    - 1934 Sep.11-1934 Dec.26 (Box 68, Folder 1237)
    - 1935 Jan.9-1935 Mar.30 (Box 68, Folder 1238)
    - 1935 Apr.9-1935 Sep.28 (Box 68, Folder 1239)
    - Death of C.W.H.II, 1935 Oct.10-1935 Oct.14 (Box 68, Folder 1240)
    - Death of C.W.H.II, 1935 Oct.15-1935 Oct.16 (Box 68, Folder 1241)
    - Death of C.W.H.II, 1935 Oct.17-1935 Oct.31 (Box 68, Folder 1242)
    - Death of C.W.H.II, 1935 Nov.1-1935 Nov.29 (Box 68, Folder 1243)
    - Death of C.W.H.II, 1935 Dec.3-1935 Dec.31 (Box 68, Folder 1244)
    - 1936 Jan.7-1936 Mar.31 (Box 68, Folder 1245)
    - 1936 Apr.7-1936 Sep.29 (Box 68, Folder 1246)
    - 1936 Oct.15-1936 Dec.26 (Box 68, Folder 1247)
    - 1937 Jan.1-1937 Mar.29 (Box 68, Folder 1248)
    - 1937 Apr.6-1937 Jul.26 (Box 68, Folder 1249)
    - 1938 Mar.19-1942 Jul.15 (Box 68, Folder 1250)
    - n.d. (Box 68, Folder 1251)
  - From: Diedrich Jansen Haines
    - 1888 Apr.26-1918 Oct.10 (Box 69, Folder 1252)
    - 1919 Ju.7-1927 Feb.5 (Box 69, Folder 1253)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1928 Jan.20-1928 Aug.28 (Box 69, Folder 1254)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1928 Sep.9-1928 Oct.15 (Box 69, Folder 1255)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1928 Nov.15-1928 Nov.23 (Box 69, Folder 1256)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1928 Dec.13-1928 Dec.28 (Box 69, Folder 1257)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1929 Jan.5-1929 Jan.29 (Box 69, Folder 1258)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1929 Feb.2-1929 Feb.25 (Box 69, Folder 1259)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1929 Mar.3-1929 Mar.30 (Box 69, Folder 1260)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1929 Apr.4-1929 Apr.22 (Box 69, Folder 1261)
    - Travel to Europe and Africa, 1929 May 21-1929 Jul.3 (Box 69, Folder 1262)
    - Depression, Death of C.W.H., 1930 Feb.25-1930 Dec.27, 1935 Oct.23 (Box 69, Folder 1263)
  - To: Diedrich Jansen Haines
    - 1882 Mar.12-1891 Dec.17 (Box 70, Folder 1264)
    - 1892 Jan.4-1892 Nov.7 (Box 70, Folder 1265)
    - 1896 Jun.19-1902 Sep.20 (Box 70, Folder 1266)
    - 1920 Apr.4-1929 Nov.15 (Box 70, Folder 1267)
    - 1930 Jan.27-1930 Feb.1 (Box 70, Folder 1268)
    - 1931 Feb.21 (Box 70, Folder 1269)
    - 1934 Jan.31-1936 Dec.25 (Box 70, Folder 1270)
    - 1937 Jan.26-1940 Jul.8 (Box 70, Folder 1271)
  - From: Robert Bowne Haines III
    - 1901 Mar.28-1906 (Box 71, Folder 1272)
    - Choate School, 1910 Oct.9-1911 Oct.15 (Box 71, Folder 1273)
    - Choate School, 1912 Jun.16-1913 Sep.25 (Box 71, Folder 1274)
    - 1922 Jun.1-1937 Dec.29 (Box 71, Folder 1275)
    - 1938 Feb.11-1939 Dec.14 (Box 71, Folder 1276)
    - 1940 Jan.6-1940 Dec.14 (Box 71, Folder 1277)
    - 1941 Jan.13-1941 Feb.26 (Box 71, Folder 1278)
    - 1943 Mar.10-1945 Apr.26 (Box 71, Folder 1279)
    - 1946 Feb.13-1963 Oct.25 (Box 71, Folder 1280)
  - To: Robert Bowne Haines III
    - 1912 Jul.5-1919 Dec.31 (Box 72, Folder 1281)
    - 1920 Mar.5-1920 Dec.31 (Box 72, Folder 1282)
    - 1921 Jan.14-1921 Dec.31 (Box 72, Folder 1283)
    - 1922 Jan.7-1922 Sep.28 (Box 72, Folder 1284)
    - 1922 Oct.2-1922 Oct.31 (Box 72, Folder 1285)
    - 1922 Nov.1-1922 Dec.28 (Box 72, Folder 1286)
    - 1923 Jan.2-1923 Mar.31 (Box 72, Folder 1287)
    - 1923 Apr.2-1923 Aug.31 (Box 72, Folder 1288)
    - 1923 Sep.11-1923 Dec.20 (Box 72, Folder 1289)
    - 1924 Jan.21-1924 Sep.22 (Box 72, Folder 1290)
    - 1924 Oct.1-1924 Nov.29 (Box 72, Folder 1291)
    - 1924 Dec.2-1924 Dec.24 (Box 72, Folder 1292)
    - 1925 Jan.7-1925 May 15 (Box 72, Folder 1293)
    - 1925 Jun.8-1925 Dec.5 (Box 72, Folder 1294)
    - 1926 Jan.6-1926 Jul.27 (Box 72, Folder 1295)
    - 1926 Aug.7-1926 Dec.28 (Box 72, Folder 1296)
    - 1927 Mar.15-1927 Dec.15 (Box 72, Folder 1297)
    - 1928 Jan.7-1928 May 25 (Box 72, Folder 1298)
    - 1928 Jun.6-1928 Dec.29 (Box 72, Folder 1299)
    - 1929 Jan.2-1929 Mar.24 (Box 72, Folder 1300)
    - 1929 Apr.2-1929 Jul.26 (Box 72, Folder 1301)
    - 1929 Aug.21-1929 Nov.30 (Box 73, Folder 1302)
    - 1929 Dec.2-1929 Dec.28 (Box 73, Folder 1303)
    - 1930 Jan.22-1930 Jun.23 (Box 73, Folder 1304)
    - 1930 Jul.2-1930 Dec.23 (Box 73, Folder 1305)
    - 1931 Jan.7-1931 Mar.27 (Box 73, Folder 1306)
    - 1931 Apr.22-1931 Dec.9 (Box 73, Folder 1307)
    - 1932 Jan.1-1932 Mar.31 (Box 73, Folder 1308)
    - 1932 Apr.1-1932 Sep.16 (Box 73, Folder 1309)
    - 1932 Oct.3-1932 Dec.30 (Box 73, Folder 1310)
    - 1933 Jan.4-1933 Mar.24 (Box 73, Folder 1311)
    - 1933 Apr.24-1933 Aug.30 (Box 73, Folder 1312)
    - 1933 Sep.1-1933 Oct.24 (Box 73, Folder 1313)
    - 1933 Nov.1-1933 Dec.27 (Box 73, Folder 1314)
    - 1934 Jan.2-1934 Feb.26 (Box 73, Folder 1315)
    - 1934 Mar.4-1934 Jul.31 (Box 73, Folder 1316)
    - 1934 Aug.3-1934 Sep.30 (Box 73, Folder 1317)
    - 1934 Oct.6-1934 Dec.26 (Box 73, Folder 1318)
    - 1935 Jan.1-1935 Apr.30 (Box 73, Folder 1319)
    - 1935 May 6-1935 Jul.20 (Box 73, Folder 1320)
    - 1935 Aug.3-1935 Oct.22 (Box 74, Folder 1321)
    - 1935 Nov.1-1935 Dec.29 (Box 74, Folder 1322)
    - 1936 Jan.1-1936 May 25 (Box 74, Folder 1323)
    - 1936 Jun.10-1936 Jul.29 (Box 74, Folder 1324)
    - 1936 Aug.1-1936 Dec. 24 (Box 74, Folder 1325)
    - 1937 Jan.8-1937 May 22 (Box 74, Folder 1326)
    - 1937 Jun.2-1937 Aug.30 (Box 74, Folder 1327)
    - 1937 Sep.3-1937 Oct.28 (Box 74, Folder 1328)
    - 1937 Nov.2-1937 Nov.30 (Box 74, Folder 1329)
    - 1937 Dec.1-1937 Dec.30 (Box 74, Folder 1330)
    - 1938 Jan.3-1938 Feb.26 (Box 74, Folder 1331)
    - 1938 Mar.3-1938 Apr.30 (Box 74, Folder 1332)
    - 1938 May 3-1938 Jun.30 (Box 74, Folder 1333)
    - 1938 Jul.1-1938 Aug.29 (Box 74, Folder 1334)
    - 1938 Sep.1-1938 Nov.29 (Box 74, Folder 1335)
    - 1938 Dec.1-1938 Dec.31 (Box 74, Folder 1336)
    - 1939 Jan.3-1939 Feb.28 (Box 75, Folder 1337)
    - 1939 Mar.2-1939 Mar.31 (Box 75, Folder 1338)
    - 1939 Apr.1-1939 May 31 (Box 75, Folder 1339)
    - 1939 Jun.1-1939 Aug.30 (Box 75, Folder 1340)
    - 1939 Sep.1-1939 Oct.30 (Box 75, Folder 1341)
    - 1939 Nov.4-1939 Dec.30 (Box 75, Folder 1342)
    - 1940 Jan.3-1940 Mar.27 (Box 75, Folder 1343)
    - 1940 Apr.1-1940 May 28 (Box 75, Folder 1344)
    - 1940 Jun.5-1940 Aug.27 (Box 75, Folder 1345)
    - 1940 Sep.4-1940 Dec.30 (Box 75, Folder 1346)
    - 1941 Jan.6-1941 Jan.31 (Box 75, Folder 1347)
    - 1941 Feb.2-1941 Mar.25 (Box 75, Folder 1348)
    - 1941 Apr.4-1941 May 29 (Box 75, Folder 1349)
    - 1941 Jun.1-1941 Jul.21 (Box 75, Folder 1350)
    - 1941 Aug.12-1941 Sep.23 (Box 76, Folder 1351)
    - 1941 Oct.1-1941 Dec.30 (Box 76, Folder 1352)
    - 1942 Jan.2-1942 Feb.26 (Box 76, Folder 1353)
    - 1942 Mar.2-1942 Apr.23 (Box 76, Folder 1354)
    - 1942 May 1-1942 Jul. 30 (Box 76, Folder 1355)
    - 1942 Aug.1-1942 Dec.28 (Box 76, Folder 1356)
    - 1943 Jan.7-1943 Mar.30 (Box 76, Folder 1357)
    - 1943 Apr.19-1943 Jul.27 (Box 76, Folder 1358)
    - 1943 Aug.2-1943 Sep.30 (Box 76, Folder 1359)
    - 1943 Oct.6-1943 Dec.31 (Box 76, Folder 1360)
    - 1944 Jan.1-1944 Feb.28 (Box 76, Folder 1361)
    - 1944 Mar.1-1944 Jun.27 (Box 76, Folder 1362)
    - 1944 Jul.5-1944 Oct.31 (Box 76, Folder 1363)
    - 1944 Nov.1-1944 Nov.30 (Box 76, Folder 1364)
    - 1944 Dec.1-1944 Dec.30 (Box 76, Folder 1365)
    - 1945 Jan.6-1945 Mar.29 (Box 77, Folder 1366)
    - 1945 Apr.11-1945 Jul.31 (Box 76, Folder 1367)
    - 1945 Aug.3-1945 Dec.21 (Box 76, Folder 1368)
    - 1946 Jan.4-1946 Apr.26 (Box 76, Folder 1369)
    - 1946 May 7 1946 Jun.29 (Box 77, Folder 1370)
    - 1946 Jul.1-1946 Aug.30 (Box 77, Folder 1371)
    - 1946 Sep.3-1946 Oct.31 (Box 77, Folder 1372)
    - 1946 Nov.2-1946 Dec.31 (Box 77, Folder 1373)
    - 1947 Jan.2-1947 Mar.26 (Box 77, Folder 1374)
    - 1947 Apr.2-1947 Jun.30 (Box 77, Folder 1375)
    - 1947 Jul.11 1947 Dec.31 (Box 77, Folder 1376)
    - 1948 Jan.12-1948 May 27 (Box 77, Folder 1377)
    - 1948 Jun.2-1948 Oct.19 (Box 77, Folder 1378)
    - 1948 Nov.18-1948 Dec.31 (Box 77, Folder 1379)
    - 1949 Jan.5-1949 Feb.25 (Box 77, Folder 1380)
    - 1949 Mar.16-1949 Jun.27 (Box 77, Folder 1381)
    - 1949 Jul.15-1949 Dec.13 (Box 77, Folder 1382)
    - 1950 Jan.3-1950 Mar.29 (Box 77, Folder 1383)
    - 1950 Apr.1-1950 Nov.30 (Box 77, Folder 1384)
    - 1950 Dec.4-1950 Dec.29 (Box 77, Folder 1385)
    - 1951 Jan.3-1951 Mar.30 (Box 77, Folder 1386)
    - 1951 Apr.1-1951 Jul.25 (Box 77, Folder 1387)
    - 1951 Aug.11-1951 Nov.19 (Box 77, Folder 1388)
    - 1951 Dec.4-1951 Dec.31 (Box 77, Folder 1389)
    - 1952 Jan.1-1952 Feb.21 (Box 77, Folder 1390)
    - 1952 Mar.4-1952 May 28 (Box 77, Folder 1391)
    - 1952 Jun.3-1952 Dec.31 (Box 77, Folder 1392)
    - 1953 Jan.3-1953 Jun.7 (Box 78, Folder 1393)
    - 1953 Jul.6-1953 Oct.27 (Box 78, Folder 1394)
    - 1953 Nov.9-1953 Dec.31 (Box 78, Folder 1395)
    - 1954 Jan.9-1954 Jan.28 (Box 78, Folder 1396)
    - 1954 Feb.6-1954 May 28 (Box 78, Folder 1397)
    - 1954 Jun.7-1954 Dec.23 (Box 78, Folder 1398)
    - 1955 Jan.4-1955 Mar.31 (Box 78, Folder 1399)
    - 1955 Apr.7-1955 Aug.20 (Box 78, Folder 1400)
    - 1955 Sep.9-1955 Dec.21 (Box 78, Folder 1401)
    - 1956 Jan.7-1956 Dec.28 (Box 78, Folder 1402)
    - 1957 Jan.3-1957 Dec.30 (Box 78, Folder 1403)
    - 1958 Jan.16-1958 Dec.30 (Box 78, Folder 1404)
    - 1959 Jan.10-1959 Dec.29 (Box 78, Folder 1405)
    - 1960 Jan.4-1960 Mar.31 (Box 78, Folder 1406)
    - 1960 Apr.1-1960 Jun.30 (Box 78, Folder 1407)
    - 1960 Jul.14-1960 Dec.27 (Box 78, Folder 1408)
    - 1961 Jan.1-1961 Mar.31 (Box 78, Folder 1409)
    - 1961 Apr.1-1961 Aug.31 (Box 79, Folder 1410)
    - 1961 Sep.5-1961 Dec.18 (Box 79, Folder 1411)
    - 1962 Jan.3-1962 Mar.28 (Box 79, Folder 1412)
    - 1962 Apr.10 1962 Dec.29 (Box 79, Folder 1413)
    - 1963 Jan.1-1963 Apr.18 (Box 79, Folder 1414)
    - 1963 May 16-1963 Aug.31 (Box 79, Folder 1415)
    - 1963 Sep.5-1963 Oct.20 (Box 79, Folder 1416)
    - 1963 Nov. 1-1963 Dec.29 (Box 79, Folder 1417)
    - 1964 Jan.1-1964 Feb.29 (Box 79, Folder 1418)
    - 1964 Mar.10-1964 Jun.30 (Box 79, Folder 1419)
    - 1964 Jul.2-1964 Oct.23 (Box 79, Folder 1420)
    - 1964 Nov.7-1964 Dec.26 (Box 79, Folder 1421)
    - 1965 Jan.1-1965 Mar.25 (Box 79, Folder 1422)
    - 1965 Apr.5-1965 May 31 (Box 79, Folder 1423)
    - 1965 Jun.1-1965 Dec.31 (Box 79, Folder 1424)
    - 1966 Jan.1-1966 Dec.25 (Box 79, Folder 1425)
    - 1967 Jan.5-1967 Sep.11 (Box 79, Folder 1426)
    - n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1427)
    - n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1428)
    - n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1429)
    - n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1430)
    - n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1431)
    - n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1432)
    - n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1433)
    - n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1434)
  - From: Mary Troth Haines
    - 1934 Sep.2 (Box 81, Folder 1435)
  - To: Mary Troth Haines
    - 1900 Feb.25-1900 Apr.20 (Box 81, Folder 1436)
    - Missionary meeting, 1933 Jun.20-1939 Aug.30 (Box 81, Folder 1437)
    - 1940 Aug.26-1949 Aug.14 (Box 81, Folder 1438)
    - 1950 Feb.2-1954 Mar.22 (Box 81, Folder 1439)
    - 1961 Sep.3-1966 Nov.21 (Box 81, Folder 1440)
    - 1969 Jan.23-1969 Dec.31 (Box 81, Folder 1441)
    - 1970 Jan.3-1970 Dec.29 (Box 81, Folder 1442)
    - 1971 Jan.1-1971 Dec.11 (Box 81, Folder 1443)
    - 1972 May 25-1973 Sep.19 (Box 81, Folder 1444)
  - Alphabetical File
    - Lizzie H. B.
    - "Miss Bacon", 1925 (Box 82, Folder 1445)
    - Ball, Alwyn, Jr., 1935 Dec.2
    - Bancroft, Wilfred, 1934 Oct.16
    - Bartelt, Fred, n.d. (Box 82, Folder 1446)
    - Becket, Mary, 1691
    - Bergoo, Fiskien K., 1879 Nov.2
    - Blair, W. A., 1883 Jan.5
    - Bockius, Morris R., 1887 May 10 (Box 82, Folder 1447)
    - Bowne, Elizabeth, 1798 Jan.27-1831 Jan.9
    - Bowne, Hannah, 1676 Jun.2
    - Bowne, H. H., 1872 (Box 82, Folder 1448)
    - Bowne, John, 1690
    - Bowne, John, 1778, 1889
    - Bowne, Mary, 1691 (Box 82, Folder 1449)
    - Bowne, Robert, 1773-1829
    - Bowne, Samuell, 1698 (Box 82, Folder 1450)
    - Bowne, Sarah, 1838
    - Bowne, T. W., 1850
    - Bowne Family Papers (copies), 1675-1891 (Box 82, Folder 1451)
    - Boyd, John, 1792-1813 (Box 82, Folder 1452)
    - Browne, Margaret M. C., 1894
    - Brown, Mary Waln (II), n.d.
    - Brown, Mary W. Wistar, 1848 (Box 82, Folder 1453)
    - Brown, (Reverend), 1901
    - Brownback, Henry M., 1927
    - Byrd, Richard E., 1941 (Box 82, Folder 1454)
    - Carnahan, Alice, 1927
    - Carroll, Charles, 1831
    - Carvill, William, 1629 (Box 82, Folder 1455)
    - Cathrall, Edward, 1751
    - Clark, E. A. (Mrs.), 1908
    - Clark, Joseph, 1908 (Box 82, Folder 1456)
    - Collins, B. S., 1839
    - Collins, Charles, 1893
    - Collins, Hannah, 1847 (Box 82, Folder 1457)
    - Collins, Lester, 1924-1926
    - Comstock, Elizabeth, 1872
    - Cope, R. R., 1861 (Box 82, Folder 1458)
    - Cosand, (Mrs.)
    - Creeth, Celia, 1885-1890
    - Donaldson, Mary Ann, n. d. (Box 82, Folder 1459)
    - Drinker, Henry S., 1811-1907
    - Farnum, E. W., 1845 (Box 82, Folder 1460)
    - Fuedzalida, G. Gilbert, 1930
    - Gamble, William, 1849 (Box 82, Folder 1461)
    - Garrigues, Abraham M., 1829
    - Gill, John, 1919
    - Gilpin, (Miss), 1905 (Box 82, Folder 1462)
    - "Grandson, My dear", 1835
    - Hacker, Hannah J. Wistar, 1917 (Box 82, Folder 1463)
    - Haines, Charles H., 1919-1949
    - Haines, Ella (Mrs. D. Jansen), 1928, 1935 (Box 82, Folder 1464)
    - Haines, Francis Cope, 1898
    - Haines, Henry Cope, 1864-1887 (Box 82, Folder 1465)
    - Haines, John S., 1806-1809 (Box 82, Folder 1466)
    - Haines, Josiah, 1784 (Box 82, Folder 1467)
    - Haines, Katharine W., n.d.
    - Haines, Margaret W., 1926-1955 (Box 82, Folder 1468)
    - Haines, Mary Drinker Cope, 1836-1886 (Box 82, Folder 1469)
    - Haines, Mary H., 1899, 1916-1934 (Box 82, Folder 1470)
    - Haines, Mary H., 1936-1940 (Box 82, Folder 1471)
    - Haines, Mary H., 1941-1945 (Box 82, Folder 1472)
    - Haines, Murray C., 1937-1940 (Box 82, Folder 1473)
    - Haines, Reuben Cope, 1868 Sep.20-1879 Mar.11 (Box 83, Folder 1474)
    - Haines, Reuben Cope, 1886 Dec.29-1909 Dec.23 (Box 83, Folder 1475)
    - Haines, Reuben Cope, 1917 Jan.3-1917 Dec.14 (Box 83, Folder 1476)
    - Haines, Reuben Cope, 1918 Jan.17-1918 Jul.24 (Box 83, Folder 1477)
    - Haines, Reuben Cope, 1919 Sep.4-1919 Dec.18 (Box 83, Folder 1478)
    - Hartshorne, Elizabeth B., 1828-1837 (Box 83, Folder 1479)
    - Hartshorne, Jane L., 1843
    - Hartshorne, Susan Ustick, 1821
    - Hawkins Co., Frank, 1916-1917 (Box 83, Folder 1480)
    - Haydock, Ellenor, 1696
    - Hepburn, William, 1785-1786
    - Henry, T. Charles (Mrs.), n.d. (Box 83, Folder 1481)
    - Hopkins, Beulah, 1829, 1837
    - Hopkins, G. T., 1832
    - Howell, Samuel C., 1948 (Box 83, Folder 1482)
    - Huston, C. L., 1928
    - Jacob, Israel, Jr., 1783
    - "Jimmy, My dear", 1903 (Box 83, Folder 1483)
    - Johnston, Edward R., 1924
    - Jones, Hannah, 1802-1826
    - Jones, Samuel F., 1826 (Box 83, Folder 1484)
    - Keagy, John M., 1820
    - Kendall, Lydia Jones W., 1878
    - Kennedy, Bridget, 1922-1932 (Box 83, Folder 1485)
    - Kennedy, Bridget, 1933-1934 (Box 83, Folder 1486)
    - Kennedy, Bridget, 1935 (Box 83, Folder 1487)
    - Leake, Frank (Mrs.), 1904 (Box 83, Folder 1488)
    - Longstreath, 1892
    - Lowber, John C., 1829
    - "Lucy", 1861 (Box 83, Folder 1489)
    - "J.M.", 1782
    - Maclure, William, 1830
    - Marshall, Benjamin, 1762, 1806 (Box 83, Folder 1490)
    - Marshall, Sarah, 1778
    - Matlack, Josiah, 1798-1799
    - Miller, Isabelle Haines N., 1919-1939 (Box 83, Folder 1491)
    - Minturn, Mary Ann, 1818-1820 (Box 83, Folder 1492)
    - Minturn, Sarah, 1815-1821
    - Morris, Anthony, 1790 Aug.14-1790 Sep.15 (Box 84, Folder 1493)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1812 Mar.26-1812 Apr.12 (Box 84, Folder 1494)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1813 Jul.31-1813 Oct.21 (Box 84, Folder 1495)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1813 Nov.14-1813 Dec.31 (Box 84, Folder 1496)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1814 Jan.8-1814 Feb. 27 (Box 84, Folder 1497)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1814 Mar.16-1814 Aug.4 (Box 84, Folder 1498)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1814 Sep.9-1814 Dec.30 (Box 84, Folder 1499)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1815 Jan.1-1815 Mar.30 (Box 84, Folder 1500)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1815 Apr.2-1815 Jun.16 (Box 84, Folder 1501)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1815 Jul.3-1815 Sep.12 (Box 84, Folder 1502)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1815 Oct.3-1815 Oct.28 (Box 84, Folder 1503)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1815 Nov.2-1815 Dec.23 (Box 84, Folder 1504)
    - Morris, Anthony, 1816 Jan.2-1816 Jul.17 (Box 84, Folder 1505)
    - Morris, Jonathan, 1769, 1798 (Box 85, Folder 1506)